Hi, I'm Yori Kobayashi. My name is Aya Ozawa.
Where am I today?
It's raining a little bit, but I'm here.
I'm here at Tokyo Visual Arts College.
Aya is holding this for me right now.
I was wondering if you could help me put up the posters for the auditions
We received your application and we would like to put it up.
We received your application, and we actually came to put up the posters
We actually came to put up the posters.
So we came to put up the posters.
I am nervous.
No, I am nervous.
It seems that he is a teacher who applied for this poster.
He seems to be a teacher.
A teacher.
Yes, sir.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Pleased to meet you.
Please.
Why did you apply this time?
Well, I teach a vocal class.
One of my students found this.
I wanted to encourage more people to apply.
It's very nice.
Boltra also applied.
I'm looking forward to it. Maybe some of the students here
to be able to work with us.
to work with us one day.
I hope this poster will be a trigger for them.
But you don't know about this, do you?
Yes, I know.
I'm itching to.
Wow!
You've been itching for it, too.
What's wrong?
May I come in earlier today? Then may I already interrupt you earlier today?
Yes, you may.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Please do.
Excuse me.
Oh, there are a lot of people here.
I'm so nervous.
You know me.
I don't know.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's artistic.
It doesn't feel like a school.
It's really stylish.
Hello.
Wave.
Thank you very much.
I'm nervous. We're kind of nervous, too.
It's amazing. Slowly, slowly, slowly.
So slowly, slowly, slowly.
It doesn't happen very often.
Going to a school other than the one we go to.
That's right.
Hello. I'm sorry to bother you.
Hello.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous. I wonder if it's okay.
Nervous?
I'm so nervous.
My hands are sweating.
Will the poster get wet?
Oh, man.
Wow, I wonder how it's going to feel. Great, I wonder what it's like.
My teacher said music.
Awesome music.
Oh, my God! We could practice, couldn't we?
I can dance.
I feel like dancing.
It's like when we're having lessons.
I want to take lessons here.
We can dance here.
It's a big space to rehearse.
I'm nervous.
Everyone's so close to the members.
I'm going to come into the classroom a little bit more.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Right around here, on the edge.
Break time.
Slash
a discussion of the five senses
Nyahahahaha
It's cute that you're so plainly nervous.
I've been feeling a little nervous lately, and it's showing on the surface.
Oh, that's good!
I've been told that it's hard to tell when I'm nervous.
That's right.
They say, "You're nervous right now, aren't you?
I totally understand, now that you mention it.
I don't know why.
But it makes me happy. It's like a sign of age.
I've always been mature, of course I'm mature now, but...
Of course I'm nervous.
You're cute.
He's cute.
I'm nervous.
Thanks for your hard work.
I'm so nervous.
That's all. That is all.
If you'll excuse me.
Good morning.
Good afternoon.
Nice to meet you.
I am Shiori Kubo from Nogizaka46.
I am Aya Ogawa.
Nice to meet you.
I'm glad to meet you. I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad. My hands are shaking.
We were holding auditions for the 6th term,
We were wondering if we could put up posters at the school,
I'm here at night.
I'm sorry. I think I was on break.
I'm sorry. I came at such a time.
I was wondering if you would let me put it up,
Is that okay?
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
Let's go!
What do you usually study?
I am currently a graduate in visual arts.
Video!
I do video editing and filming,
I have heard many times about Nogizaka-san's example.
Thank you very much. I'm glad.
Who is it?
I'm Ayaka.
Ayaka.
And you are Ayaka?
Are you in the media too, Ayaka?
I am a founder of the Music Creation Department.
Founding?
I'm a founder. Founding.
That's great!
Yes, it is.
Then, I'll totally come.
Someday, then.
Maybe we can meet at the show someday.
Will I?
Good luck, Aya!
All right!
Okay, this way.
Yo!
It's in! I got it!
Yes!
It's hard, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
It worked!
Yes!
Thank you very much.
So, this is how it looks.
Amazing. It's right after you enter.
They have entered.
They were in.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much.
What do you think?
It means that the person who sees this could be 6 years old.
That's right.
But even if you come in at 6 years old,
Aya's sister?
That's right.
High school? High school now?
I'm in my first year of high school.
I'm in my first year of high school!I'm in the first year of high school!
He's cute.
He's cute, isn't he?
Yes, it is.
She is cute.
I'm looking forward to seeing them,
I am looking forward to it.
I hope this poster will be a good start.
Also, look at the date!
Look at the date.
What is today?
It's Nonaka's birthday.
Oh, my!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
I think it's fate that we were able to make it a memorable day for you,
Please feel free to visit us.
As Aya mentioned,
I hope you will feel free to apply.
I'll be waiting for you.
I am waiting for your application.
We are now at Risshisha High School.
We are here.
Well then, let's get started,
Let's go.
I'm so excited.
Hey! I'm so excited!
I've never been to school in person before.
That's not good.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I will start the audition poster.
In this corner, I would like to introduce a student from my class, Yuuki Nakajima.
I love Nogizaka and went to their concerts many times.
I heard that many students in my class also love them and often sang karaoke with them.
Please give my best regards.
I am nervous. I am nervous.
I am too nervous.
I have a lot of hurdles.
So many pictures.
It says Natsui Seishun.
Just in time.
I might run like crazy. Guys.
I can't wait to get home.
Gyukko!
Yes, sir. So, I'd like to go to the 22nd grade of Nakajima-sensei's class, 2C, right away.
I'm nervous.
It's my first time. Like this.
I'm scared, scared, scared.
I'm already there.
Oh no. What should I do?
What should we do? What should we do?
I'm scared.
I'll go anyway.
Excuse me.
I'm Nogizaka46.
I am Nogizaka46.
I'm here today to put up posters for the 6th term audition that Mr. Nakajima applied for.
We are here to put up the posters.
It looks like this.
Anyone know about the audition for the 6th term?
Really? Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Who likes Nogizaka?
Thank you very much. I'm glad to hear that.
There are some girls who are not so confident or who are not brave enough to join Nogizaka,
Today, I would like to talk about the good things about joining Nogizaka,
What do you think?
What are some good things about joining Nogizaka?
My life has changed completely.
I had a position here in Kyoto,
I even volunteered to sit in this seat and study alone during breaks, I volunteered to study there, and I even spent all my break time studying in this seat by myself,
I was alone all the time,
But after joining Nogizaka, I gained so many important things,
I am so happy to have met my fans,
I think there are many of you who are in the second year of high school and are wondering about your future,
I know that many of you are in your second year of high school and are wondering about your future scene,
I think there are many of you who are now in your second year of high school and are not sure about your future, but I think that there is a new way for you to go to college like I did,
I would be very happy if you all could apply.
I was the youngest person ever to join the group,
I was 12 years old at the time,
I had just graduated from elementary school,
I still have to go to junior high school for the next three years,
I was 12 years old at the time, and I had just graduated from elementary school,
I was 12 years old at the time, but I had just graduated from elementary school,
There were a lot of hardships,
I had a lot of hardships, but I had never met so many people before,
I met a lot of people I would have never met if I hadn't joined the group,
I met a lot of people I would have never met if I had not joined,
I met a lot of people that I would have never met if I had not joined the company,
You don't have confidence, do you?
I don't have confidence.
I don't think there are many people who like me either,
I don't think there are many people who like me, but because I meet people who support me, I am able to like myself,
Or, a part of you that you disliked can become your strength,
So I think this is a place where you can come to like yourself even if only a little,
If you are interested, I would be happy to have you take the class.
Is the pressure ok?
Is there pressure?
It's red, so there is pressure, right?
My hands are shaking.
We are also very nervous.
I don't know how to talk to them.
If there is something you want to ask, we will answer.
I don't know if any of you have been to a live concert before.
I have.
Handshake meeting?
I see.
Whose handshake, by the way?By the way, whose?
Kin-chan.
I see.
Do you dance while singing NV or something?
Is it hard work?
Yes, it is hard work.
There is a difference between those who are physically fit and those who are not,
But when we go to a live concert, everyone has to move the same amount,
Of course, there are places where you don't pay attention to your body shape,
Of course, there are some things you don't pay attention to, like your body shape, but you have to eat well and build up your strength.
It was hard work, wasn't it?
Thank you very much.
I hope you will join us, too.
What is your favorite Nakasaka song?
What's your favorite song?
There is someone I want to talk to right now,
Since I got to know Nakasaka 46,
I think it is one of my most favorite songs and I have fond memories of it.
I like the Under songs a lot,
The first song I participated in as an Under
A New World is my memory.
I like it?
I'm glad.
Thank you.
I can relate to it.
I'm glad.
I love it.
Do you have a favorite song, sir?
I'm glad.
It's great.
She sings something that doesn't exist here.
It's not good.
Is it very difficult to sing something that doesn't exist here?
The tempo is too fast.
The tempo is fast and difficult.
I would like to put up posters,
Put them up together.
Together.Together.
I'm so happy.
I'm going.
I was told I'm small.
That's not good.
It's true.
Okay, I'll go.
Where do you want to go?
Here?
Come on.
You want it down there?
Thank you.
I put up the posters right away.
Thank you very much.
They put it up together.
They put it up.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
I'm waiting for your application by all means.
Thank you very much.